Largely software
as a service.
Now, if there's
something wrong with
this chart, you
can see it
is in our
projection for software
as a service
going forward on
the top there,
20% plus.
It's not going
to be anything
like that. In
fact, we do
believe that software
as a service
is becoming a
victim of this
AI revolution. There
will be consolidators
and software as
a service providers
who do survive
this route.
They will consolidate
the market.
But we
underestimated ourselves.
We were saying
that SaaS was
going to
lose share.
We didn't realize
how much, how
soon. And that
gives you a
sense of how
quickly this revolution
is happening.